本片荣获2024年\N戛纳电影节《最佳剧本》奖
穆比娱乐
火柴工坊
英国进行式电影公司
黑匠影业
穆比娱乐\N\h荣誉出品
英国进行式电影公司\N制作发行
联合制作\N《黑匠》电影团队
【新星】伊丽莎白·斯巴克
《点亮你人生》【主持人】伊丽莎白·斯巴克
【女卫生间】维修中 禁用
【男卫生间】
伊 丽 莎 白
【某种物质】
它改变了我的人生
【鲜花标签】感谢多年相伴 怀念往昔 那时的你太赞了
【那时的你…】
【诚聘】想成为下一个伊丽莎白·斯巴克吗\h\N只要：青春漂亮 活泼可爱 年限18~30岁
【编号503 芯片卡】
【北拜伦巷35号】
【激活剂】
【一次性使用 用后即扔】
【稳定剂】另一个自我使用
【转换针 滴管】
【基体营养液 完美体营养液】
【慎重提示】你只能激活一次
【你必须每天注射稳定剂】
【特别提示】每七天转换一次 没有例外
【牢记】你们是一体
【稳定剂】基体抽取 每天注射一节
【注射7-7节】
【扔掉的报纸 电视台招聘广告】
苏
【注射7-6节】
【即将推出】新人 新秀
【第三天】
【注射7-5节】
【注射7-4…3节】
【第六天】
【注射7-1节 最后一天】
【每七天交换一次】
【基体营养液 即将耗尽】
【转换针 滴管】
【完美体营养液】
【日历上标记"自我与苏"日期】
【某种物质】您的补充套件已经送达 在您的快递柜
【即将推出】新人 新秀
【每七天交换一次】
【破例】
【喝醉了 摩托留你这儿 :- ）——特洛伊】
来吧 和苏一起【扭动】
【某种物质】您的补充套件已经送达 在您的快递柜
【美体交往的——特洛伊】
【废旧物品 伊丽莎白】
【弗雷德 电话323-555-0102】
【伊丽莎白 废旧物品】
【和苏一起来扭动】
【弗雷德】我到餐厅了 你要晚到会儿吗
【弗雷德】我知道你肯定想闪亮登场 :)
【弗雷德】你没事吧
【墙上卷纸】它改变了我的人生
《法国美食》
【圣歌版本】
【奥伯哈克 土豆泥拉丝】
3个月后
【迎新年 "夏娃秀"】明晚九点
【鲜花标签】祝好运 观众会爱死你的
【明晚9点】
【营养液混用】
滚开
【某种物质】您的终止套件已经送达 在您的快递柜
- 你知道… - 滚远点
【某种物质】很遗憾 未能让您满意
【终断剂】
【鲜花标签】祝好运 观众会爱死你的
【迎新年 "夏娃秀"】今晚九点
【终止剂】
【牢记】你们是一体
【迎新年 "夏娃秀"】今晚九点
【观众会爱死你的】
【女士专用室】
【激活剂】一次性使用 用后即扔
【怪物】伊丽杀苏
【鲜花标签】祝好运 观众会爱死你的
【迎新年 "夏娃秀"】今晚九点
【开播】
【残星】伊丽莎白·斯巴克
某种物质
编剧与导演\N科拉莉·法尔雅
主 演\N黛米·摩尔
主 演\N玛格丽特·库里
主 演\N丹尼斯·奎德
制片人\N科拉莉·法尔雅 蒂姆·贝文 埃里克·菲尔纳
执行制片人\N尼古拉斯·罗耶
执行制片人\N亚历山德拉·洛威
制片总监\N萨拉-简·赖特
摄影指导\N本杰明·克拉昆
音乐创作\N拉弗蒂
电影剪辑\N科拉莉·法尔雅 杰罗姆·埃尔塔贝 瓦伦丁·费隆
副导演\N马修·德拉莫蒂埃
艺术指导\N斯坦尼斯拉斯·雷德莱
服装设计\N埃马努埃莱·尤奇诺夫斯基
化妆与监督\N皮埃尔-奥利弗·珀森
音乐指挥\N吉尧姆·鲍雷斯
特效制作\N让·米尔 保罗·德斯科因 罗拉·罗恩
特效监制\N伯纳德·布里登 皮埃尔·胡格尼
单元制片经理\N本杰明·塞利兹
后期制作主管\N亚伯拉罕·戈德布拉特 蒂瓦·纳钦
剧务主管\N吉尧姆·勒梅尔 托马斯·格罗斯
色彩师\N法比恩·帕斯卡
视觉特效\N布莱恩·琼斯 皮埃尔·普罗库丁·戈尔斯基
视觉特效\N切尔文·沙法吉 纪尧姆·勒古埃兹
声音录制\N埃马纽埃尔·维拉德
声音混响\N斯蒂芬·蒂博 维克多·普劳德
声音剪辑\N瓦莱丽·德卢夫 维克多·弗勒兰
拟音师\N格雷戈里·文森特
字体设计师\N吉尔斯·波因特
伊丽莎白 看这里 请看这里 伊丽莎白 我们爱你 爱你\N- Elizabeth - Over here - Look here please - Elizabeth - We love you - We love you
你能行\NYou got it!
感受那股力量 女士们\Nfeel that power, ladies!
记住 膝盖要压下去 你可以的\NAnd mark, get those knees down, you got it!
一起来\NCome on!
踢臀 转身\NButt! Hip!
没错 你做得很好\NOh yeah, you got it!
挺直 想象你穿着比基尼泡在海水里 你想\NSquare! Think about those bikini bathes you wanna...
看着像只沙滩上的水母一样\Nlook like a giant jellyfish on the beach
继续\NCome on!
伸展\NPush!
你可以的 坚持住女士们 你们能行\NYou got it! Hang in there ladies, you got it!
你可以的\NYou got it!
锻炼完成 宝贝们\NToday's worked out baby!
好了 我们下周见\NAll right then hope I'll see you next week
下次的《点亮你人生》我们将锻炼小腹部分\Nfor Sparkle You Life, we 're gonna work on the latter labs
也是最难塑肌的部位\Nyou know, the most difficult part to sculpts
与此同时 照顾好自己\Nbut at the mean time, take care of yourselves
完事儿 一号位\Nwork's fine, position one
干得漂亮 谢谢大家\NGreat jobs,ladies!
- 大家辛苦了 - 很不错\N- You got it! - Nice one
生日快乐\NHappy birthday.
谢谢\Nthank you
哦 谢谢\NOh, thank you.
生日快乐\NHappy birthday.
谢谢\NThank you.
我不管你们是否要把镇上的小姑娘全找一遍\NI don't care if every fucking young girl in the fucking town
几周内给我完成\Nin these few weeks.
听着 我说的很简单了\NLook, I made it simple.
找年轻的\NWe need her young.
身材辣的\NWe need her hot.
马上去给我找\NWe need her now.
怎么能让那黄脸婆主持这么久\NHow the old bitch has been able to stick around for this long.
我他妈就不明白了\NThat's the fucking mystery to me.
哦得了吧 得过奥斯卡也得擦屁股滚蛋\NOh, Oscar winner, my ass.
再说得奥斯卡那是多少年前了 \NWhen was that back in the 30s?
怎么 就因为一部《金刚》\NWhat, for King Kong?
不 鬼才记得给过她承诺\NNo, I don't give a fuck what we promised her.
这是网络电视节目\NThis is network TV,
不是傻逼慈善项目\Nnot a fucking charity.
赶紧给我找新人\NFind me somebody new.
快 \NNow.
嘿 你知道女人25岁后就开始衰败了吗 \NHey, did you know that a woman's fertility starts to decrease by the age of 25?
珍妮弗都几岁了 \NHow old is Jennifer?
你最好赶快\NYou better get busy.
看着张老脸在电视上 就跟屏幕上沾了屎一样\NIt's like when you see someone fart on screen.
人们喜欢的是美女\NPeople just love that.
懂吗 这种节目就得小年轻干\NI mean, that's just the way it is.
你能听懂吧 \NSo you know what I mean?
人的本性不会变\NPeople are just people.
我就得按照人的本性来做\NAnd I have to give people what they want.
股东也喜欢这么做\NThat's what keeps the shareholders happy.
而人们更是喜新厌旧\NAnd people always ask for something new.
不得不换人\NRenewal is inevitable.
等到了50岁\NAnd at 50, well,
就绝经了\Nit stops.
绝什么 \NWhat stops?
嗯 \NWhat?
你说绝什么 \NWhat stops?
嗯 你知道 就是…\NUm, you know, the um...
嗯…\NThe um...
哦 乔治 \NOh, George!
哦 哦 \NOh, oh!
- 抱歉 我得走了 - 哈维 \N- I'm sorry, I gotta run. - Harvey!
乔治 节目收视率太赞了 \NGeorge! Those ratings are insane!
你真是天才\NYou're a genius!
哦 这有点乱\NOh, what a mess.
你太牛了\NYou're a genius.
所以才来庆祝\NThat's why you'd be drinking.
哦 太搞了\NOh, that's hilarious.
斯巴克女士 您走运了\NWell, it's your lucky day, Miss Sparkle,
我们对您进行了全身扫描\Nbecause we have X-rayed you from head to toe,
您并没有任何牙隐裂\N and you don't have so much as a crap molar.
您可以离开了\NSo, you are good to go.
嗯 疫苗已接种 好\NUh, vaccination, okay?
没有度假计划 \NNot going on a vacation.
对了 我老婆 她是您的忠实粉丝\NBy the way, I just want to say, my wife is a huge fan.
嗯 血型…\NUm, blood type...
哦 嘿 今天是您的生日\NOh, hey, it's your birthday.
生日快乐\NHappy birthday.
哦 是紧急呼叫 抱歉 我得去…\NOh, uh, that's an emergency, I'm sorry. I, uh, had to have a...
再见\NBye.
稍等\NOne moment.
最后一项检查有点…\NIt's just one last exam to perform.
你刚才不是说我没事了吗\NI thought he said I was good to go.
有问题吗 \NIs there a problem?
没有 一切都很好\NNo, it's perfect.
您是我们的绝佳人选\NYou're a good candidate.
我是说 您要离开了吗\NI mean, are you good to go?
祝您好运\NI wish you the best.
莉兹 \NLizzie?
莉兹·斯巴克 \NLizzie Sparkle?
天啊 不敢相信\NOh my God, I can't believe it.
费雷德\NFred!
十年级大课同班的弗雷德\NFred, from 10th grade homeroom!
哦 弗雷德 我当然记得\NOh, Fred, of course.
你真是一点没变啊\NYou haven't changed a bit.
还是这世上最美的姑娘\NYou're still the most beautiful girl in the whole wide world.
知道吗 我跟随你进了同个行业\NYou know, I followed your career.
你可太成功了\NWhat a success.
我是说 哇 哇 哇\NI mean, wow, wow, wow.
哇\NWow.
嘿 不如我们一起去\NHey, why don't we go out
抽空喝几杯\Nmaybe for a drink sometime
既然都 又遇见了 保持联系 \N now that we're, you know, reconnected?
嗯…\NUm...
哦 对 我的错\NOh, of course, I'm stupid.
你肯定很忙\NYou're super busy.
不过\NBut you know what?
不如你把名片给我\NWhy don't you give me your card?
还是说你 你没带…\NI mean, you never help.
嗯 行 多可惜\NUm, sure, what I...ah
这个体检单给你也行\NThis will do. Oh.
别看我的胆固醇指数 简直是场灾难\NDon't look at my cholesterol levels. They're a disaster.
哦 天啊\NOh, God.
这是啥 \NWhat is that?
给吧\NThere.
现在 有我名片了\NNow you've got it.
你有没有梦想过\NHave you ever dreamt
成为华丽的自己\Nof a better version of yourself?
更年轻\NYounger.
更美丽\NMore beautiful.
更完美\NMore perfect.
只需一次注射就能解放你的DNA\NOne single injection unlocks your DNA,
开始新的细胞分裂\Nstarting a new cellular division
创造出另一个自己\Nthat will release another version of yourself.
试试"某种物质"\NThis is the substance.
以你为基体\NYou are the matrix.
创造一切\NEverything comes from you.
享有一切\NAnd everything is you.
一个更华丽的自己\NThis is simply a better version of yourself.
只需相互分享\NYou just have to share.
一周是老的你\NOne week for one
一周是新的你\Nand one week for the other.
交替七天的完美平衡\NA perfect balance of seven days each.
只需牢记\NThe one and only thing not to forget.
你们是一体的\NYou are one.
你无法躲避你自己\NYou can't escape from yourself.
喂 \NYes.
你好\NHello.
我想订购\NI'd like to order.
地址\NAddress.
贝弗利峡谷街1057号\N1057 Beverly Canyon.
来这个地方：北拜伦巷35号\NWrite this down: 35 North Byron Alley.
35号\N35 North.
以你为基体\NYou are the matrix.
创造一切\NEverything comes from you
享有一切\Nand everything is you.
一个更加\NThis is simply
华丽的自己\Nbetter version of yourself.
你好\NHello.
谢谢\NThanks.
下周我们会通知你\NWe'll let you know by next week.
感谢\NThank you so much.
我很渴望这个机会\NI'm just dying to get the part.
很棒的舞者\NGreat dancer.
嗯 可惜 看她脸 不如直接看那对奶子\NHmm, too bad her boobs aren't in the middle of her instead of the nose.
下一位 \NNext!
这次感觉各方面都完美无瑕啊\NLooks like everything sure is in the right place this time.
请告诉我们 姓名 年龄 三围\NPlease say your name, age, measurements.
我叫苏\NI'm Sue.
我叫苏儿\NI'm Sue.
苏 苏 苏 苏 苏 苏 苏 苏 苏 苏 苏\NSue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue.
苏 苏 苏 苏 苏\NSue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue.
她在哪 \NWhere is she?
她在哪儿 \NWhere is she?
多么美艳的天使\NWhat a gorgeous little angel.
你被录取了\NYou're hired.
我们的节目就需要你这样的人\NWe want a show that's just like you.
美丽快乐 蠢蠢欲动\NBeautiful and happy.
人们都想开心\NPeople want to be happy.
两周后开播 开始准备吧\NWe air in two weeks, so let's get to work.
剩下的交给我的助理就行\NI'm gonna let you organize the rest with my assistant. uh...
- 她叫… - 伊莎贝拉\N- uh... - Isabella?
以…依…伊莎\NIs-is-isis.
破名字念着都费劲对吧 \NWho has time to say that?
以后就叫你辛迪得了\NWe're gonna make you Cindy.
名字更短 也更方便\NIt's shorter, it's better.
就这样 辛迪就是你 会得到周详安排 去吧\NSo, I'm gonna let you organize everything else with Cindy.
哦 对了 走之前\NOh, um, before you go,
我有一个小问题\NI just have to mention a...
关于我的档期安排\Nsmall scheduling issue.
我必须每隔一周去城外一趟\NI have to be out of town every other week
照顾我母亲\Nto take care of my mother
她病得很严重\Nmother, who's very sick.
只要你来做这个节目\NI want you for this show
你妈也好 你兄弟也好\Nand we will work around any mother, brother,
甚至阿猫阿狗 不管什么病 尽管放心\Nfucking sick, puppy you need to take care of.
懂吗 \NHmm?
懂吗 \NHmm.
人美 还心地善良\NGorgeous, with a pure heart.
观众肯定会喜欢\NPeople are gonna love that.
很好\NPerfect.
跳跃 环胸 \NSo you jump out, touch your elbows,
低下头 拉伸\Nhead down, contract.
五六七八 环胸\NAnd five, six, seven, eight, elbows.
你去哪了 \NWhere have you been?
我一直想找你喝一杯 给你送行\NI've all been wanting to have a drink with you for your departure.
总而言之\NAnyway,
我们… 众筹了下\Nwe uh...all chipped in
给你准备了点小礼物 供你消遣\Nand we got you just a little something to keep you busy.
这可是本法语书\NIt's French.
我老婆 她还为此生气了\NMy wife, she's for her spire.
哦 我可不想惹她\NOh, I don't want my wife.
糟了 我得走了\NOops, I gotta run.
很高兴 要是还能再见到你\NBut it's always great to see you.
像羚羊和鹿角在你肌肤上移动\NThe antelope and the deer moving about
这可不是纸上谈兵\Nare going through the text.
这些按摩角还可远程操控\NThe antelope with remotes.
竟然只卖49块9\NI cannot believe the incredible price for I.98.
混蛋 别弄噪音了 别人还要睡觉 \NGod damn it, lady, come on! I have to sleep at the sweet night.
开门 \NOpen up.
快开门 \NWe gotta open up.
嗯 不好意思\NAnd uh, sorry.
我以为是斯巴克那老太太\NI thought that Ms. Sparkle.
她搬走了\NShe moved out.
我是新租客\NI'm the new tenant.
苏\NSue.
奥夫\NOlver.
奥利夫\NOver.
奥利弗\NOliver.
你找我有事儿吗 \NYou wanted to complain about something?
奥利弗\NOliver?
怎么会 \NWhat?
没事儿\NNo.
没没没没没没没\NNo, no, no, no, no, no, no.
就是\NI think it's
感觉很好\Nlike awesome
听着那些装修工具嗡嗡响 你能懂吗\Nwhen there's stuff going on in the building, you know what I mean?
嗯 事实上我还\NUm, I'm actually,
我动手能力还挺强的 如果你需要帮忙\Nquite handy if you ever need,
或者需要各种援助、急救…\Nneed me to be of aid in any way. Ummm...
我一大袋子工具呢\NI got a sack of tools and...
还有个大榔头\Nand a big hammer.
你懂我意思\NYou know what I mean.
总之 我也住这儿\NAnyways, I live right here,
有需要就来找我\Nso you know where to find me.
随叫随到\NAnytime.
不分昼夜\NDay or night.
以后见\NLater.
嗨各位\NHi everybody.
我是苏 是时候动起来啦\NI'm Sue and it's time to pump it up.
准备好了吗 \NAre you ready?
开始\NLet's go.
感谢各位\NThank you so much everybody.
我们下周见\NI'll see you next week.
与此同时\NAnd in the meantime,
大家要保重哦\Ntake care of yourself.
真有礼貌 \Ncourtesy!
太绝了 太绝了\NWonderful, wonderful.
我不会待太晚 等我下\NI won't be out late, so just wait for me.
别吃太快\NDon't eat too fast.
你还好吗 \NAre you all right?
没事 马上回来\NYes, I'll be right back.
你干什么去了 \NWhat did you do?
你看着比之前还要美\NYou've seen me the more beautiful than before.
不\NNo.
喂\NYes.
喂 你好\NYes, hi.
我是伊丽莎白·斯巴克\NThis is Elizabeth Sparkle.
503号\NI'm 503.
请讲\NYes.
嗯 你好\NYes, hi.
我用某种物质时没算好时间\NThere's been a slight misuse of the substance.
额外多用了一个小时\NA few extra hours were accidentally used
结果手指 嗯…变异了\Ncausing umm... an alteration.
我想知道该怎么把它恢复原样\NSo I'm just looking for the procedure to reverse it.
另一个你消耗的时间 到你身上就没了\NWhat has been used on one side is lost on the other side
没办法补救\NThere's no going back.
不 我不知道她是怎么想的\NNo, I don't know what she was thinking.
而且显然她是喝醉了\NAnd obviously she was drunk.
牢记 没有你和她之分\NRemember there is no she and you.
你们是一体的\NYou are one.
遵循平衡\NRespect the balance
就不会有任何差错\Nand you won't have any more inconveniences.
♪ 你难道不知道 不知道 不知道 不知道 ♪\N♪ Don't you know, know, know, know ♪
♪ 你难道不知道 ♪\N♪ Don't you know ♪
♪ 你得动起来 ♪\N♪ You got to pump it up ♪
♪ 你难道不知道 不知道 不知道 不知道 ♪\N♪ Don't you know, know, know, know ♪
♪ 你难道不知道 ♪\N♪ Don't you know ♪
♪ 你得动起来 动起来 动起来 动起来 ♪\N♪ You got to pump it up, pump it up, pump it up, pump it up ♪
♪ 动起来 动起来 动起来 ♪\N♪ pump it up, pump it up, pump it up ♪
♪ 你得动起来 ♪\N♪ You got to pump it up ♪
苏 \NSue!
苏 \NSue?
我在电视上看见你了\NI just saw you on TV.
我勒个去\NHoly moly.
看得我想报你的班了\NMakes me want to join your class.
嘿 你不开私教课吗 \NHey, you don't give private lessons, do you?
嘿 嗯…\NHey, ummm...
要不要来我家里喝点酒 \NWhat about a drink at my place tonight?
来啊 别害羞\NCome on, don't be shy.
我知道你就站在门后 大美人\NI see you standing behind the door there, gorgeous.
行吧\NAll right,
慢慢来 但记得我约了你哦\Ntake your time, but it's a date.
你懂的 动起来\NYou know, pump it up
你得动起来\NYou got to pump it up
苏\NSue.
来点什么 \NWhat can I get you?
摩卡拿铁\NMoka Latte.
很难熬 对吗 \NIt's long, isn't it?
你说什么 \NExcuse me?
七天很难熬\NSeven days.
你跟踪我来的吗 \NDid you follow me here?
我就是好奇\NI was just curious
好奇你发生了什么\Nto find out how things were going for you.
每一次你都感觉更加\NEach time you feel a little more...
孤独\Nlonely,
不是吗\Ndon't you think?
我不知道你在说什么\NI don't know what you were talking about.
我很好\NI'm fine.
万事如意\NEverything's fine.
每一次都会更加困难\NIt gets harder each time
记住 你还值得活在世上\Nto remember that you still deserve to exist.
再丑陋的你也是你\NThat this part of yourself
也有活着的意义\Nis still worth something
你还值得\Nthat you still matter.
她已经开始了吗 \NHas she started yet?
开始蚕食你了吗 \NEating away at you?
操 \NFuck!
小心点 \NWatch out!
看什么 \NWhat?
嘿 \NHey!
滚啊 \NMove!
你依然是这世上最美的姑娘\NYou're still the most beautiful girl in the whole wild world.
你好 \NHello?
嗨 弗雷德\NHi, Fred.
我是莉兹\NIt's Lizzie.
喂 \NHello?
抱歉 我 我呆住了\NSorry, I mean, I'm a chalk.
哦\NOh.
哇\NWow.
哇 哇\NWow, wow.
我还以为永远都接不到你电话…\NI thought I'd never hear from you again after-...
哦 天 别 不是 我只是 有点\NOh gosh, no, no, not at all. I just, I've just...
最近有点忙不开\NI've just been really busy lately.
我想说 我在想\NSo listen, I was thinking that
我们有空可以一起聚一聚 \Nmaybe we could get together and grab a drink?
你还在听吗 \NAre you still there?
抱歉 我…我又惊呆了\NSorry, I'm, I'm, I'm in shock again.
那我定路易吉餐厅 8点行吗 \NI could book Luigi's at eight?
8… 那就8点 路易吉餐厅见\NEi...Ei...Eight in Luigi's it is.
啊 我…我们晚上见\NUh I... I will see you tonight.
拜拜\NBye.
好的 拜\NOkay, bye.
嗨 各位\NHi everybody.
嗨\NHi.
好了 大家注意 场地就位\NOkay, here we go everyone. Clear the set please.
第一机位 谢谢\NFirst positions, thank you.
运镜开始\NRoll cameras.
三 二 一\NAnd in three, two, one.
下蹲 下蹲 下蹲\NSquat, squat, squat.
屁股扭一圈\NCircle those hips.
拉伸 拉伸 拉伸 拉伸 拉伸 拉伸\NContract, contract, contract, contract, contract, contract.
抱头下腰\Nhead between your legs.
停\NCut.
不好意思 我以为 我以为 我\NI'm sorry, I thought I, thought I, I,
我走神了\NI just got distracted.
没关系 再回退一遍\NNot a problem, let's get right back to it.
从一机位开始\NBack to one please.
打扰一下 管理室找\NSorry, it's the control room now.
导演说他从监控器看到奇怪的东西\NThe director said he saw something bizarre on the monitor.
摄像机重播一下 二号位\NBring up the replay on camera two.
二号机\NCamera two.
快进\NForward.
我能换上礼服吗 \NCan I have my dressing gown?
抱歉 礼服在更衣室\NSorry, it's in your dressing room.
那你快去拿去啊 \NWell go and and get it.
慢慢播 一帧一帧\NLet's just take this frame by frame.
给我五分钟\NI need five minutes.
喂\NYes.
平衡没效了\NThis balance is not working.
我压根没时间享受\NI barely have anytime to enjoy myself
而她却能虚度七天\Nwhile she wastes seven days
整日把脸埋电视机里\Nstuffing her face in front of the TV.
牢记没有你和她之分\NRemember there is no she and you.
爱你们\NI love everybody.
怎么了 \NWhat's happening?
人呢\NWhere is everybody?
节目取消了\NThe TV's been canceled.
- 什么 为什么 - 苏\N- What, why? - Sue.
哈维要你马上去办公室\NHarvey wants to see you in his office immediately.
知道了\NOkay.
我会让他改变主意\NI'll go change him.
不 他让你马上去\NNo, he said now.
我就开门见山了\NI'll get right to the bond.
你不能一直做早间节目\NWe can't keep you on the morning show.
为什么 我才刚做起来\NBut why? I just started.
收视率登顶了\NRatings are through the roof.
我们从42点开始\NWe started at 42.
一路飙升到现在 大概…\NNow we're up to like--
216点\N216.
太惊人了\NIt's phenomenal!
大家喜欢你\NPeople love you!
爱慕你\NThey adore you.
他们想看更多更多的你\NThey want more and more and more of you.
所以我们决定\NThat is why we have decided
你将作为主持\Nthat we want you
主持今年的跨年"夏娃秀"演出\Nto host the New Year's Eve show.
你你你你你是说…\NYoooou mean the...
电视网最大的演出\NThe network's biggest show.
五千万人在线观看\N50 million viewers live.
你甚至能收视更高\NYou can't go higher than that.
但时间紧迫\NThat's gonna be intense.
只有一两个月时间准备\NWe only have a few months to pull it off, so,
你愿意吗\Nare you in?
只有你给运气开了门\NIf you don't open the door and opportunity knocks,
才能有机会抓住它\Nyou won't get another chance.
你(或是我)都知道这点\NYou of all people know this.
多要一天 就有整周的时间\NJust one more day and then I have a whole week off.
可以按时交换\NWe can switch.
还要去拍《时尚》杂志封面写真\NWe're doing the cover of Vogue.
就再多一天 行吗 \NJust one more day, okay?
- 是的 - 她没有遵守平衡\N- Yes. - She didn't respect the balance.
她窃取了我更多的时间\NShe's stealing more and more time from me,
压根不计后果\Ncompletely without consideration of the consequences.
她就是个自私的婊子\NShe's a selfish bitch.
那你要终止吗 \NWould you like to stop?
终止\NStop.
你是基体\NYou are the Matrix.
如果你不满意\NIf you are not satisfied,
你可以终止体验\Nyou can put an end to the experience
重回自己本身\Nand go back to being just you on your own.
确定要终止吗 \NWould you like to stop?
我会回到之前的样子吗 \NWill it go back to the way it was before?
已经转换的无法返还\NWhat has been transferred won't come back,
但你可以终止体验\Nbut you can stop the experience.
现在 你还要终止吗 \NAs of now, would you like to stop?
重回自己本身\NTo go back to being just you on your own?
不\NNo.
不 不 不\NNo, no, no.
不能终止\NI can't stop.
只是她…\NShe just--
必须要遵循平衡\NThe balance just needs to be respected.
那就遵循平衡\NSo respected.
停下 停下 停下 停下 停下\NStop it, stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it.
你是赢家\NYou are the winner.
恭喜 你已经赢得了2万5千美元奖金\NWell, congratulations, you've won %,000.
我们还有最后一关\NWe'll have one final chance
一个问答题\Na simple question
答对了就能再进一步 或得25万美元\Nin our big question round and play for %0,000.
而这道题 你只有45秒的时间作答…\NAnd you'll have just 45 seconds to come up...
操\NFuck.
真牛\NBoss.
是的 女士们先生们 她来了 \NYes, ladies and gentlemen, she is here.
今日顶流女星 苏 \NThe superstar of the moment, Sue.
准备好了吗 \NAre you ready?
掌声有请 苏 \NLet's welcome her, Sue.
你像不知哪冒出来的龙卷风一样 席卷所有荧屏\NYou popped up nowhere on our screens like a tornado.
谁都没有预料到你的出现\NI don't think anybody was really prepared for this world.
从早间节目升起的新星\NIt all started with the morning show
有传言称 你会参演汤姆·格兰特的下一部电影\Nand rumor has it that you are up for Tom Grant's next movie.
稍等片刻\NWait, just a moment.
我被告知 你将主持今年的跨年晚会\NI'm being told that you are going to host the New Year's Eve show.
你能证实这个消息吗 \NCan you confirm this?
是的 没错\NYes, that's right.
我的天啊 重大新闻\NOh my God, that is huge news.
跟我们聊聊你自己吧\NTell us a little bit about yourself.
你家是哪的 \NWhere are you from?
怎么被挖掘出来的 \NHow did you get discovered?
我想知道 我们所有人都想知道你的一切\NI want, we want to know everything.
其实 我也没什么能说的\NWell, I mean, there's really not very much to tell.
毕竟只是一个\NI'm just a girl from a
从印第安纳州 走出来的小女孩\Nvery small town in Indiana.
我家的小镇 你们都不一定听说过\NI'm sure that you've never heard of it.
事实上 连个镇子都算不上\NIn fact, it's not even a town.
我都不确定 它算不算得上村子\NI'm not sure you could really even call it a village.
一个农场 可以吗 \NIt's a farm, perhaps?
但从我记事起\NBut ever since I can remember,
登上荧屏就是我的梦想\Nit has always been my dream to be on screen.
我的梦想才对\NThis is my dream.
小时候 我会表演节目给家人看\NAs a child, I used to put on shows for my family.
呃 你的家人\NMm, your family.
真贴心\NHow sweet.
那 大家都注意到 你顶替了伊丽莎白·斯巴克的位置\NSo, everyone is aware that you replaced Elizabeth Sparkle.
毫无疑问 你一脚插了进来\NAnd no doubt about it, you stepped in,
还把收视率提高到了不同的量级\Nyou turned up the volume,
风靡全世界\Nand you rocked their world.
那你原来是斯巴克的粉丝吗 \NWere you a fan of her show?
嗯 我 我不能 嗯\NUm, well, well, I can't, uh,
其实不能说我看过她的节目\NI can't really say that I actually watched her show.
要知道 我们毕竟压根是不同时代的人\NYou do know that we're not exactly from the same generation.
必须承认的是\NAnd you have to admit, it
那些节目都老掉牙了\Nit was a bit old-fashioned.
简直是侏罗纪活化石\NJurassic Fitness, really.
它们的问题就是得与时俱进\Nthe problem is it needed a change.
我他妈要给你看看\NI'll fucking show you.
你想看侏罗纪活化石 \NYou wanna see some Jurassic Fitness?
你想看\NYou want it?!
来啊 来看看你他妈的侏罗纪活化石\NCome on, come get your fucking Jurassic Fitness!
但我母亲是她的铁粉\NBut my mother was a huge fan of hers.
所以每个大清早 晴天雨天\NSo, every morning, rain or shine,
她的《点亮你生活》都在电视上播放着\NSparkle, your life, was on TV.
所以一定程度上 我是和她一起成长的\NSo, in a way, I grew up with her.
不论我喜不喜欢\NWhether I liked it or not.
可能这也是你这么说的原因\NI guess that's why you could say
我们有着某种联系\Nwe have some sort of connection.
某种联系\NSome sort of connection.
没了我 你压根就不存在\NYou wouldn't exist without me.
邦 邦 邦 邦 邦\NBum, bum, bum, bum, bum.
时间到了 女士们先生们 最后一个问题\NIt is time, ladies and gentlemen, for our final question.
也是我们每个人都想问\NThe question that we ask
- 甚至每个嘉宾都要问的问题 - 好的\N- each and every one of our guests. - Okay.
你能和我们稍微分享一下你的美丽秘诀吗 \NWould you share one of your little beauty secrets with us?
稍微一点点\NJust one little trick of yours
你能保持如此美貌的秘诀\Nthat helps you look so incredibly stunning.
你本人是多么漂亮\NI mean, look at you.
我也不知道 就…\NI don't know. Uh...
说出来\NSay it!
让我想想\NLet me think.
告诉他们 你的美丽秘诀\NTell them who your little beauty secret is!
- 我想 - 怎么不敢直接说啊 \N- I guess, - why don't you just show them right here?
这就是你的美丽秘诀\NHere's your little beauty secret.
我想我只是敢于做自己\NI guess I just try to be myself.
真诚 感激自己拥有的一切\NTo be sincere and grateful for all that I have.
牢记随着自己的内心生活\NAnd to always remember to live with my heart.
哦 甜进我心窝去了\NOh, I'm here at the sweetheart center.
我只是 嗯 哦 敢于做自己\NI just, woo, oh, I try to be myself.
停下 \NStop it!
停下 \NStop it.
你从我这抢走了\NYou're taking it from me.
你的美是从我这抢走的\NThat's your little secret.
停下 停下 停下 停下 停下 停下 …\NStop it! Stop it! Stop it! Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!......
你必须克制你自己\NYou have to control yourself!
我不能回去 要是我终止…\NI can't go back, if I turn....
哦\NOh.
恶心的老东西\NGross old rat.
停下 \NStop it!
上床吗 \NComing to bed?
好 马上来\NYes, I'll be right there.
喂\NYes.
嗨 嗨 紧急情况 我…\NHi, hi, this is emergency. There's a...
我没有稳定剂了\NThere's no more stabilizer fluid.
喂 \NHello?
我是他妈的503号\NIt's fucking 503.
知道\NYes.
操 \NFuck!
我说了这是紧急情况\NI'm telling you, this is urgent.
我稳定剂用完了\NThere's no more stabilizer fluid.
那说明你到最后阶段了\NIt means you've reached the end.
你什么意思 \NWhat do you mean the end?
你已经消耗完了\NYou've drained it all out.
如果你还想要更多 必须等它重生\NIf you want more, you must let the fluid regenerate.
告诉我该怎么做\NTell me how to do it.
我现在就需要稳定自己\NI need to stabilize myself right now.
你只需要换回来就行\NYou simply have to switch.
你说什么 \NExcuse me?
换回来后 就能开始恢复稳定剂\NThe switch reboots the fluid secretion process
然后你便能继续体验\Nso you can continue to enjoy the experience.
不 不 不 不 不\NNo, no, no, no, no.
我不能转换 我不能\NI can't switch, I can't.
尤其是现在\NEspecially not now.
你别无选择\NThere is no other option.
苏 \NSue?
宝贝 \NBabe?
你还好吗 \NYou all right?
要不我明天再来 \NShould I start about tomorrow?
宝贝 \NBabe?
苏 \NSue?
哪里不对劲吗 \NIs something wrong?
你看起来有点暴躁不安 是工作的事儿吗 \NYou look cranky, because your related business?
苏 开下门\NSue, open the door.
快啊 苏 \NCome on, Sue.
这不好玩 我也要小便\Nnot funny, I need to take a pee.
苏 开门\NSue, open the door.
开门 苏 快开门\NOpen the door, Sue, come on.
开门 快开门\NOpen the door, come on.
什么玩意儿 \NWhat the fuck?
给我滚开 \NGet the fuck out!
你是谁 你他妈是谁 \NWho's this? Who the fuck is that?
离我远点 \NLeave me alone!
卧槽 什么鬼 \NWhat the fuck?
喂 \NYes?
我是503号\NIt's 503.
我想终止\NI want to stop.
你确定吗 \NAre you sure?
一旦终止 便不能退回了\NOnce you stop, you can't go back.
我想要终止 我他妈要终止 \NI want to stop! I want to fucking stop!
我要终止 \NI want to stop!
我们知道了\NWe'll deliver.
你确定吗 \NAre you sure?
一旦终止 便不能退回了\NOnce you stop, you can't go back.
你会保持你自己的模样\NYou will simply remain on your own.
重回自身\NJust on your own.
重回自身 自身 自身 自身\NJust on your own. on your own. on your own.
- 他妈的闭嘴 - 自身\N- Shut the fuck up! - Your own.
好了\NOkay.
我不能…我做不到\NI can't... I can't do this.
我需要你\NI need you.
我需要我自己\NI need myself.
你 你快 你得准备好 今晚是属于我们的\NYou, you got, you gotta get ready. It's our big night.
快啊 他们会特别爱你\NCome on. They're gonna love you so much.
快啊\NCome on.
快\NCome on.
你是我唯一被爱的部分 你必须醒过来\NYou're the only lovable part of me. You have to come back.
快醒过来 快点\NYou have to come back. Come back.
没事 没事\NOkay. Okay.
快啊\NCome on.
快\NCome on.
不要\NOh, don't!
你们知道发生什么了吗 化妆组 \NYou guys know what happened, makeup?
这人 你得跟我们去隔间\NHere, we gotta get you the pinning room.
还有最后一个舞台测试 灯光 音响\NWe have one final test on stage, of lighting and sound.
在演出前 我们留在外面\Nnow we wait outside before show starts.
你看行吗 \NYou got it?
- 嗯… - 没事吧 \N- En... - You good?
没事 走吧\NOkay, let's go.
真美\NGrab it.
风韵十足\NWonderful.
准备惊艳全场吧\NThere you go.
还好吗 \NYou good?
你等会儿要跳舞吗 女士 \NYou gonna dance, lads?
抱歉 我马上回来\NI'm gonna be right back, sorry.
苏 他们要你去台上测灯光效果\NSue! They need to see you on stage to test the light.
你有没有梦想过\NHave you ever dreamt
成为更华丽的自己\Nof a better version of yourself?
更美丽 更完美\NMore beautiful, more perfect.
苏 \NSue?
好的 我们舞台上见\NYes, let me meet you there.
没事 我们台上见\NOkay, so I'll wait for you on stage.
苏 \NSue?
来见见我们的股东们\NLet me introduce you to the shareholders.
他们对你期盼已久\NThey have been dying to meet you.
有什么问题…吗 \NIs everything...okay?
那就微笑\NSo smile.
我们今晚就要你笑出来\NThat's what we want tonight.
尤物就该保持微笑\NPretty girls should always smile.
羽毛诱惑 羽毛诱惑 羽毛诱惑 \NFeathers! feathers! feathers!
嘿 准备好了吗 \NHey, you ready for tonight?
你能成为更华丽的自己吗 \NWould you be the better version of myself?
请让我更美丽 求求了 \NPlease give me a better version of myself, please!
求求了 \NPlease!
变美 \NCome on!
这次感觉各方面都完美无瑕啊\NLooks like everything sure is in the right place this time.
请告诉我们 你的姓名 年龄 三围\NPlease say your name, age, measurements.
我叫…\NI'm...
尤物就该保持微笑\NPretty girls should always smile.
可出来了 我们都等急了\NAt last, we're starting to worry.
快点 从五号机位前上台\NHurry up, you're up in five.
她来了 真美啊\NThere she is, so beautiful.
我们爱你\NWe love you.
这才是你的舞台\NThis is where you belong.
这永远都是你的舞台\NYou always belong here.
没有你我们什么都不是\NWe can't do it without you.
没有你我们一事无成\NWe'll never do it without you.
你会把所有人比下去\NYou are here to replace them all?
女士们 快 上台\NGirls, come on, let's go.
还在等什么 \NWhat are we waiting for?
- 快啊 - 都快点 快走 快走\N- come on! - Everybody, let's go, let's go, let's go.
你肯定不会失望\NYou will not be disappointed.
她可是我最美的杰作\NShe's my most beautiful creation.
是我一手造就了她\NI have shaped her for success.
五 四 三 二 一\NFive, four, three, two, one.
怪物 \NThe monster!
快杀了它 \NShoot the monster!
怪胎 \NIt's a freak!
- 别怕 - 怪物 \N- Don't be scared. - Monster!
是我啊 \NIt's still me!
是我 \NIt's me.
我是伊丽莎白 我是苏…\NI'm Elizabeth, I'm Sue.
怪胎 \NFreak!
怪胎 怪物 怪物 \NFreak, monster, monster!
是我啊\NIt's me.
不 我只是…\NNo I'm just...
可惜不能像看她脸一样 直接看她那对奶子\NToo bad her boobs aren't in the middle of her face instead of that nose.
下一位 \NNext!
尤物就该保持微笑\NPretty girls should always smile.
50岁后\Nat 50.
就绝经了\NIt stops.
真漂亮\NSo beautiful
我们爱你\NWe love you.